[{"answer": "NEEDLES CENTER", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Call the ball?  I don't see the ship", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Bring it left. Bring it left, You're high", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What is", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Wait! Hell!..Something's wrong", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Were upside down", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "We're on vapor, Cougar, you got to put it down", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "TELL HIM, WILL YOU TELL HIM? OUR INSTRUMENTS ARE OKAY", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Need a hint", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You like to work alone. I've heard that about you", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You like to work alone. I've heard that about you", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "And you were with Cougar. He was my roommate in flight school", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What, what is it", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Never mind mine. Check hers", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "The family unit", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I've been married since I was eighteen. Why don't you believe me", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You saw a MiG 21", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I saw one", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I saw a MiG do a 4 G negative dive", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You saw a MiG 21", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Where did you see that", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "It never came up", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You seemed determined to do that anyway.. Why didn't you tell me you were a famous MiG insulter? MAVERICK Would it have made a difference", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I'm special", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Give me a break, I'm asking you out", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "A date... Coffee... A drink...A walk in the park", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What plane", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " You're horribl", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You don't have to kill it", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Somebody does. It's more honest this way. You do your own dirty work", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "About as much as they think about killing me", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I always wanted to fly... ever since I first saw a jet. I wanted to fly jets, then I wanted ", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "And now I want you", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Pulled left, rolled out, underneath", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "That's because you don't have any women", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "That's he", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Bad", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "It's my own way. It works for me. I don't care about the rest of that stuff", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "For the same reason you are", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Food...and you...my ", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Well no...inverse order", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I'm still second best", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I don't fly in anything that doesn't show movies", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "FIRE, OR CLEAR OUT, ICE", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "YOU GOT TOO MUCH NOSE TO TAIL", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "All right", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I know. I was there", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "You don't have to do this", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "I'm not good company. I should be alone", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "How do you play reality", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": " Strip reality! How do you play that", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Want to play the game", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "You say the truth.  Go ahead. Don't be afraid. You want to win the game, don'tcha", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "No bother", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "My wife's house", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Or you can quit", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "I didn't know either. That's why I told Jester to prepare your papers", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "I GOT A WINDER LEFT, BUT NO GOOD TONE ON IT", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "I GOT NO TONE. IT MIGHT GET YOU", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Just relax", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "The plane is fine", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Is it the plane", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Is it you", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "I guess I owe you one", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "You saved our lives. You did it", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "You don't owe me anything. We're on the same team", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "We did it", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "We did it", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": " No. You can be mine", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Well what", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "What do I want", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "What do you want", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "What do you want", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "I think they know we're here", "docId": "Top-Gun.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "Oh, no. You did the flying, I'll do the talking", "qsentId": 76}]